hapo.org 2016-03-14

# FACTS

                                                                                                            rev. 10/10
                          WHAT DOES HAPO COMMUNITY CREDIT UNION
   FACTS                  DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
                          Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law
 Why?                     gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires
                          us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please
                          read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
                          The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or
 What?                    service you have with us. This information can include:
                           Social Security Number and income
                           Account balances and payment history
                           Credit history and credit scores
                          When you are no longer a member, we continue to share your information as
                          described in this notice.
                          All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their
 How?                     everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can
                          share their members’ personal information; the reasons HAPO chooses to share; and
                          whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                                                            Can you limit this
 Reasons we can share your personal information                Does HAPO share?
                                                                                                 sharing?
For our everyday business purposes –
such as to process your transactions, maintain your
                                                                       Yes                          No
account(s), respond to court orders and legal
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes –
                                                                       Yes                          No
to offer our products and services to you
For joint marketing with other financial companies                     Yes                          No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
                                                                       No                     We don’t share
information about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
                                                                       No                     We don’t share
Information about your creditworthiness
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                     No                     We don’t share
   Questions?            Call toll-free 800-284-4276 or go to www.hapo.org

 Page 2
What we do
How does HAPO protect my       To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use,
personal information?          we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures
                               include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does HAPO collect my       We collect your personal information, for example, when you
personal information?
                                  open an account or apply for a loan
                                  make deposits or pay your bills
                                  use your credit or debit card
                               We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit
                               bureaus or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing? Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                  sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about
                                   your creditworthiness
                                  affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                  sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                               State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to
                               limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates                     Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                               financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                  HAPO has no affiliates
Nonaffiliates                  Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
                               financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                  HAPO does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you
Joint marketing                A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial corporations that
                               together market financial products or services to you.
                                  Our joint marketing partners include insurance companies
